

ABOUT ME

I am a software engineer major who's passionate about people-centered development as well as strategic decision-making.

SKILLS & QUALITIES

Programming experience C, Java, Python, Javascript, Typescript

Experience in web interface programming includes HTML, CSS. JS, SASS, SCSS, Reatcjs, Nextjs, React Native, Antd, Material-ui,

Backend programming experience includes Django, Servlet, Django Rest

Experience in making tools with selenium

Experience with tools such as Git, Gitlab, Nodejs, SQLserver, Azure, Docker, Nginx,

REACH ME AT:

PHONE NUMBER: 0972 141 556

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/giakinh0823/

GITHUB:

<u> https://github.com/giakinh0823</u>

EMAIL:

giakinh2000@gmail.com

LANGUAGE

- Vietnamese
- English

KINH HA GIA

Software Developer

EDUCATION

FPT University

2019 - present

Here I learned a lot of things. School work helps me learn languages like Java, C, Java web, Web design, .. and computer knowledge. It has helped me solve many problems before. In addition to the knowledge of programming, I also learned about skills in the working environment and a lot of interesting things here.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

10/2021 - 11/2021

I joined the frontend code project with Nextjs for the delivery startup S-ONE.

- I use TypeScript to code Nextjs.
- Use GitLab to manage and work with the team.
- I use Antd to design the website.

Full-Stack Developer

05/2021 - 09/2021

I participated in a project to code on products to buy, sell, and trade Facebook services. I do backend with Django and frontend with Reactjs.

- I use Django Rest Framework to make web API.
- For the frontend I use redux, and the redux toolkit to manage the state for the site.
- I use Material-ui to design the website.
- I use many other tools like react-route-dom, Axios, Chartjs, react-hookform....

Full-Stack Developer

02/2021 - 04/2021

I take full responsibility for the Hara startup project to participate in the FPT Edu Biz contest. Project for startups about crowdfunding. I work in the field of getting data, design, code backend, frontend.

- I use selenium tool to perform data retrieval to perform product testing.
- Use the Strapi API to make payments.
- Use channels, websocket to code messaging and notification functions for the website
- Using selenium to get data
- Use reactis as frontend

Full-Stack Developer

12/2020 - 03/2021

I work here as a product developer and creator for Scholar to participate in the FAIC 2021 conference. Here I undertake and implement the project myself. With experience through self-study and inquiry.

- Using selenium tool to get data from google site.
- I use JavaScript, the Chartis library to display word cloud, help users understand the authors.
- Using NLTK library to analyze natural language to display word cloud
- Using Docker to build the environment
- Use Celery to manage tasks, schedule time to crawl data from Google Scholar to update articles by authors.

SKILLS & QUALITIES

In addition to the experience and working with the above real projects. I also learn and practice regularly about Python, Selenium, Nodejs, Java, Django, Reactjs, Nextjs, React Native. Especially in the past time I have focused on React.

- Java: I am extremely proficient in using this language for study and tutoring.
- Python: I can code Django backend with python, crawl data with selenium
- Nodejs I have worked on a few small projects, such as product management, product deletion level 1, level 2, etc. Working with Mongodb to manage the database.
- Reactjs: then I do quite a few projects on it. I use redux, redux-toolkit, redux saga to manage states and fetch api actions. I use axios to fetch api. Also I use react-hook-form, react-router-dom,... and many other tools. I can use both Typescript and Javascript to code Reactjs. Manage and limit unnecessary re-rendering of components with memo and useCallback. Proficiently use both antd, and mui in coding the interface for Reactjs. Proficient in style scss module in Reactjs.
- Nextjs: I understand and apply the basics and fetch api for production.
 Understand SEO in Nextjs.
- React Native: Since I have a strong understanding of React, working with React Native is very easy. I use expo to code React Native. Master and understand the knowledge in React Native.